Youyou independent broadcast theater --YoYo Television Series Exclusive
So
you had together before
I told her
absolutely not just
a simple relationship between students
and nothing more
photos as well as photos of things
I know that
I borrow it is clear that
such a clever little brain
I do not want to get it
so
afraid of the water, too afraid to
do things on the water
thanks to my brother
as long as you are around
I will be very reassuring
that the last group of people quit after Johnny
took the
SA system we have now
developed FiT ready to market the
system SA to be released if they improved after the
successful listing of the words
that our technology available on the market
really no value
Ling, most of
the money invested in the
development of this kind of thing
Fang Yu construction he
is not overnight
people will be able to reach
where to start
so much money ah
fly special behind several major shareholder
groups
really do not understand is
that several major shareholders why
must invest FiT it
seems that
they really are iron to follow
the heart Ling Ling, the total
commitment of the
parties must be those people
can have high return of interest
also well
prepared to carve up the New York latitude dividends
go
to the construction of Yu Fang
good
uncle assured that you
will not
live up to everybody's
nephew we expect that
all rely Ling, a total of
scared me you you you
you you do not
stand behind me, silently
doing it your
brother usually
did not do anything good conscience, if
there is nothing to fear
me happy today
do not care about you
and your the start can be really cruel
two-pronged approach
to both the New York Wei also took the opportunity to draw
a heavy blow several major shareholders
do not know what you are talking
with a potential money Ling
Wei Group to cut New York's way out
which is really a good idea to
you think
dad would know how to do
anyway, then you tell him
that you do not have a
ghost only thing I complain nose
let me tell you
also know he is all right
just to let him see
me Ling, a casual
support small companies
can easily
put your painstaking efforts of the New Zealand latitude
to replace
you not only have to say
the future of the electricity supplier and technological
potential to do on behalf of Ling
brother let you see
the future look like in the end
you are so eager to
want to beat I
want to prove anything
to prove in the end I was the
only heir Ling's group
and you are nothing
you are not afraid it would have been
too greedy
disastrous it all but you are my cup of soup is
divided among
a face told me that
What are the consequences of
what the consequences of
greedy
funny
what happens
I think you could not eat
sour grapes, right
then I wish you all wishes come true Big brother
is not how this kid
a little nervous feeling that I
did not ah this
made me quite uncomfortable
are ready well, do
not let the guy and he is a gecko
can take advantage of
the all-pervasive
assure you
all arrangements have been made
to go
Nana babe small
Jie Jie Chi
in your department who
told me at the meeting
of hacking the
good good
company causing serious
loss and leakage current
of a large number of important documents
public Division
has scheduled back in
to retrieve data that is basically
less than thirty-five percent of
the talent and
we have two teams
have applied for resignation
effective immediately arrange
personnel need
to enter the job
what are you murder me
am I
doing exercises
to practice how you
doing coming
takeaway
prawn sister to send you a
thank you
to go super
rude
freshly grilled prawns
accompanied by the music
really must taste Oolong orange
smell the aroma yet
how
you did not eat grilled shrimp will not
you try it
you try to know
really can be delicious to
me to demonstrate it for you
to go head
to tail
to try
me I think this is
good shrimp
are not ready
to be people
how to eat delicious taste it
you wear gloves to
take away my
little sister
compliance task today
does not affect your work
I tried to get back
I will give you what
you do not send me
back to myself it is
okay
wait here while I
go wash my hands
right back
waiting for me ah
assured that I will not have
time to grab
the dog's overtime friends
quickly come to me busy
Gu Xin Er,
Long time no see
ah, ah, is the Gu daughter
often hot search on
this recently with the president of New York-wai
rumored Well who do
not Keiji you exactly how it was
with two young master
ah Langkawi who
you say you can be considered a
childhood
denied him how personally end
with you do ah
hear you're getting married.
Congratulations, you ah
this is not that
the divestment of our young master Chen now
how he would
have long since been dumped
my fiance is
my president Qin
Qin president's son
turned out to be
a VIP golf business son
badly
since you have to be married
with Master Qin
trouble you persuade him
more than two years
do not give me flowers every day
I do not want our
cleaning staff does not make sense
to do cleaning work so that every day
you must be a
nonsense to seduce you his
aunt
you all right
all right
I've said
this fairy sister
is your fiance
have been wishful thinking
bothering her
so to
go back and take control of your men
do not walk
in public Sapo
you give me this straight
who is aunt ah
how do you know I'm here
it seems I'll
have to be cautious that you
send Bo fans
may not be happy
today, ah thank you
but at this point
there is nothing
exhibition should be closed but
next time it
seemed close to home performance venues
it is my ticket right now
how I like it when you open for business
and so
rest assured that
all arrangements have been
there three hours
to fly special ceremony was about to begin
Zealand latitude there any movement it
seems to me no big movement
this brother
is stuck in the gentle village
Ling always
get out
of your way this move
really is clever diversion
I ask you ah
Ling Yue
this is not beyond resurrection
antidote
I do handsome
handsome
to fly the boss
how a special
feed now Fei
said that the
defendant
had just received special
notice
what is meant
New Zealand latitude to
steal trade secrets
lawsuit to dispute the Ministry launched a
sudden blackout
fly so
special to be properly listed
what table
Feelings
I'm afraid there is no way a
group of shareholders
happened so suddenly there
seems to have got the message
being cheap to sell
shares to fly special
gang old man running out of patience
a lawyer's letter
to shareholders lost patience
seems to be they have received an email
last night,
there are fly special
water sales data reports
that are
difficult for us to get
all of the shares
immediately outflows to hear me come back I purchased in
the growth rate of
the pied piper
commitment
to you
is
to come
Ling always
afraid that you
can not buy back shares
mean anything
that Fang Yu construction can not afford
not say you can afford buying
more importantly,
I would be willing to sell you
have to do with him
is your
release
Loosen the
security you call
a woman afraid of her total
security even if
you look at Ling came
also beat her
it did not matter as simple as
how I was feeling under the cover
you are not already planned a
big brother
you think I do not know what
you covet New Zealand Wei part of
it for a long time
I had a car accident also it dragged me
your plan so you
have time to fly special rise
good to go pry my team
stole core technology Zealand weft of
you already know
you are deliberately engage your order I
even collapse
own company's core technologies are you
willing to give me for nothing
really cruel
but you think you beat
me you did not see the core technology of
the company can hold it much longer
I FiT's largest shareholder
brother
you think you pry away
my team
took the SA system
will collapse York latitude it
actually ah
I would like to thank you
I have always felt that New Zealand latitude
staff redundant
thanks to you
to help me do my staff to streamline investment
at home and abroad have been
outstanding graduating students who
to fully automated
technology research and development
is currently effective
already invested construction
so that the so-called
SA
semi-automatic, but you
managed to create the illusion of
the original is not
just Big brother let me know
in advance the plan only
if it is not you
so aggressive greed, then
maybe
you today there
will not lose so much
if you then go on so greedy
sooner or later you will be your ambition
to eat out
anyway, you win
something sarcastic
not let you say a thing
Ling
Ling always your total
feed
your okay
not Liu Dong
I do not like that we
will not pass outside of
his boss not to
leave the country just two days before his
people on
how to do the boss
now directors are looking for you
to think about
how do I
find these days I
always see
good
Premier Zhu
Ling total
feed to the
dispute to a new department there does not have to
prove the
know
so many resumes
I have been fruitless and other social animals it
is sad to say do not worry
I'm not a thing you have not found work
for it does not work
you go back do your
lady president
or president to inherit the family business
is also good
to see you again you
you are not do not know what
you see over
there, I tell you ah
man sat down and from us
to now have been too narcissistic, right
in selfie he then
opened a mill
that looks Piga beauty
that does not take it so
Manager Zhao
acquaintances ah
do not pretend
I know you have
observed me for a long
service Member of
a cup of
white water
on it to find a job
ah
think about
it you come to our
company
to me recently resigned
ready to start your own business
just met a writer
but I think he put a little expensive
so the price
is still under consideration
do not want a new job
but is looking for Well
you can not work good
voice seems a bit big
bold Manager Zhao
told me that Zhao Lei
Zhao Jingli like or you
think about this partner
we feel at ease and let
us feel at ease, but
super online network man man
great God great God
I am not without her nonsense
What network Man great God
I'm a
rookie like to draw cartoons
only small
screen name that you are what
Northwest Chang'an
sorry ah
moment did not hold back
myself to
you like this lipstick
is not waterproof Ha you rub a
paste your Armani lipstick
I I can not
look try
not to set foot in
the Northwest recently Buyer no
idea Chang'an beauty ring ah
I have been your fan ah
eh
you still read my work ah
of course
I accidentally picked up
shortly before been chasing
but it did not take long Royal Highness stopped
me more sad for a long time this is also
how you more of it
you do not you can join
me in the studio
with copyright as long as you stake
on it
so
the studio
to studio would be
the two of us
grow up quickly
or else
let me good friends
also joined in a lengthy
slipped over her sketches
really
brothers
ah how about
a little thing
but it
can Who
Mike
is an idol
almost all of his drawing hand
drawn not all yo
know
but it does not matter
that
you would like to join
us, Miss lengthy studio you
consider
not taken into account
anyway come together to
find a job
how do you know
I can not find a
job for people who work
will get as big
as your day also
working day sitting in a cafe chatting it
okay
how about
a Naga me
that the name of our studio is
called
the Milky Way cool Man
done what
awesome
is not it a little crooked ah
ah I do not crooked
design icon
itself is a little
crooked like this
I do not doubt
that is
more beautiful
walk walk
take a look inside
how to
paint a very pretty
newly renovated ah significant expenditures
are also very good
picture of the intentions of this
line ah okay
for the peace of mind
that your station
here is the CEO
for me
yo you sit here now
why I'm here
because you are away from the door near
you can easily get take-away
is also OK
for
that place can also
put a sofa
here, then I think you can
hang a poster on
here a little bit empty
it
who it was who it was
who came
to the boss
how you
can bring me to work it
so you do not stop me
do not see eye to pack up and
do not tell me you
can not stop me nibbling a sugar
ah
Baochibaozhu
but without pay
when we sign the contract
go to dinner
ah why do you take an umbrella with
rain today
how today rain
today Chance of rain ah
so much sun
you do not see weather forecast
weather forecast I've
often are not allowed
do not look at
it today when I
have a rainy day is a
quasi-no rewards
are watching it
go go
Well now
someone to
feel at ease
and warmth is a
quick look at what
you do then the gossip
come help me a ball
today considered a bill
sunny weather
average temperature 22 degrees
at night the temperature eight
degrees, add clothing to prevent colds
actually was smart ball
after it called the Little six of
your eight petit petit six
perfect match
it with my officer that you
know you should fishes officer with
behind my learned yet
what I know
to be more than you think
you can leave it
to forget what they have
burned my microwave oven right
that is not ground gas
to earth
you are now
waiting for noon
lunch time time
to eat lunch
before the body Bang Bang Oh
how the more you like Ling
ramble
I do not go out for lunch so what
can you see me ah
do not eat on time
can cause gastritis, gastric ulcer
dyspepsia
also reduces brain function
affects the brain development
and even
lead to mental decline
line I went
to dinner I
do not say
no one filled with water
to help me do
a good
total Lingling
what
information are you ready
to come back
ready to do that
quest can
do so again go on
that capital is gone
and that in the future have no future
is the rapid collapse
Yes
if so
which do not have
any future
good
we should not quarrel
listen to me say it
the whole thing through
that we are now clear
you shareholders are
requested to express their views it
with Ling,
chairman of the board we were always
in black and white, but
he signed a treaty
for the development of the logistics
industry, said Ling potential
that only get what the company
now
not only our commitment to return
cash not
also lose all
our capital go
are a family
and we do not want the
chairman of the court
also ask you for us over the overall situation
that you want him how to do ah
we just want to return to
our original that part of
it since there is no money
to build Fang Yu's
stock lost cash
we just want
to give
you kill me chant
shut
out such a big thing
you want to follow everyone
to wash their hands do
you say
I have a better side
now battered
buildings building programs
even if they are cashed
can not make up for everyone
how much is the loss of
up to give you
a little psychological comfort
if you want,
I can put New Zealand weft
have been entitled to five percent
after dilution to give you cheap
as it was my
brother's apology to everyone
I believe we all know
New Zealand latitude soon on the market
this five percent of the
profits, but
in the future is
limitless ah
that would be a good idea ah
like to see the present situation
it is in a
good approach to ah
you can make up for some
very impressive to see the return which
gears up
Fang-yu ah this now
is a basket case
and its Sike it
would be better to choose a
promising way
out of it
that we still have to buy his shares ah
it seems
there is not much cost-effective
so that what
we now put
my big brother equity took it
to see the face of the chairman
I do not want to tangle
so we decided it
was the first
chairman of the board
you do not delay dealing with family passed the
hard work you trip the
boss
before you importune me no matter
how
you practice, but now
has been a threat to the
interests of intra-group
today Fortunately, you have a
second child fishing
or else even I can not hold your
dad know that
I know is wrong
wrong wrong where
I should not arrogant ah
from real estate to electricity suppliers
erred in failing to estimate
the risks of cross-industry
and difficulties
I'll tell you
what your mistakes is
the biggest mistake you made
was that you thought you were
aggressive this time
because of a lack of experience it
is not
your lack of vision and if you really
mind one day
sit in this group
chairman location
how you let the whole company
all employees
believe you can lead the company
forward
dad
drink water before
you first eliminate cool
brother also knew was wrong
this time you have a good rest
of the company
to temporarily forget about the
things you
told me dad
this time you really want to thank
you for your
brother, he not only helped
you to save a lot of losses Langkawi
do you know
how
to sit still
you are not satisfied
dad
company there are things that
I'll go first
you look how
your brother is doing things
you really should
take part with him
and you also learn
me how old
you are twenty-two
year of age
every day,
you follow
a girl thrust behind
what thrust it
a bit sterile
okay, etc.
you are so wary about doing it
he just helped me
I could for him how
you say
why you just help me
as long as I obviously have won
a fall of
Langkawi is what you
can hand you why this time I really want
to close the reason you do
not understand what winning or losing
is not important for me,
I do not intend to argue with you
so you aim to do
is to let me thank you is do
you think I do not care how
big brother
things have
happened, let it used to
not think too much of it you
suddenly feel nothing mean
what it means nothing
your brother I
had just experienced a roller coaster
and it was just
suddenly relaxed
brother
where are you going
to let my dad not to say I leave it to you
to listen to him
I go out
back to the company
Keiji
how good
you know you here
today in this work
so close to it
about you to run away
to elope
interested adults may not
be doing the things
I was only joking
mainly you want to discuss today
has been
you promised me a date
where you want to go to
the outskirts of
outing I know there is a
very big theme music festival
I bet you like
but I now
have the names of some of the work is not busy working
all right
anyway, I know that
you would refuse me a high probability
Since overtime, then it
is a good supplement
to eat more energy
to take care of myself
so I
thank you ah is not very
conscious, but I really have something to be busy
know you're busy this busy man
go
bye
Excuse me, sorry
I can send you I
suddenly remembered
that it's
not something
that What worried us or do we
go out and play
really fast on the train it
this is what
I do not know
that I can drink it
so sweet
to what it
does not taste good
we go
well
our comics traffic
has broken one hundred thousand
you see, you see a
comment that you see
people inside fans ask for an increase in blood more
I see
how I feel at ease with Xiaoying
suddenly found
that I actually look quite like ah
ah I just stood shining
so pretty faces do not you draw
Would not it be a waste
that I had Well
how nerve to do
it you will not
fart girl blows rainbow
are so blind to it
her face how it pie
with that oval face
is also linked to a share ah
Zhao Lei, how have you
not something I have ah
when you find that mouth
really is no need to look
perfect, I think
you would like to chat ah
scare you about it how I'm doing
on the car, right
peeping
What do you want
to celebrate your traffic
broken but I still have
one hundred thousand ah
a lot of things you do not
have to work continuously for weeks
right to own a holiday
I do not see how
other owners are
subordinate to
torture you here
to press my
self how can under torture ah
this is my boss
I was cleaning staff
What is my aunt workers are
in addition to torment
me I could torture
myself Who
do you want to take me where to
go camping
you do not mean I is not grounded gas
camping
you kinda thing Well I
would go back Zhicuojiugai
I get my drawing board
girlfriend
ah really is a workaholic
is not a long way
short of a super cute
girl ah accompany
me there were pretty boys
can barely allowed to
accompany
us
peace of mind
that we have to rest
for the Pobai I'm
ready for
a million to do when we went to
celebrate
walking up
I will not bother you
prepare it
this evening encounter her
feet the hearts of the
decision not to hear her call out
to go home with her
eyes about to
faint speak to me
slender figure in Street
Come fluttering figure
said to me quietly turn romantic lover love me
and I said it
then have to drink two bottles of water
so do not
say that beauty can
almost exploded
on a lengthy
today we went camping
can really see the kind of
sky Galaxy of stars you
can
really
I checked several times to say that
the observation point
here is certainly a lot of camping enthusiasts can see
it can see
I will not be disappointed
that I can eat this do
you want to eat What are
you thirsty
something to
drink, but do I want to eat this fat
you say this
little Sheng
brother
sister-in-law is also
a coincidence ah
coincidence
where you go
we go camping we ah
ah How about you
we are just looking for
a place to camp
or else we feel at ease
with it
a coincidence that you are
a coincidence
right ah
we also intend to go camping
with it a coincidence or else
it would be good
that I go with
my little lengthy too much
the first time
on such a successful tent
you help me take a picture chant
lines
go
well, well,
look look look look
cute yet
Zhao Lei
I have not seen it
like you are so narcissistic
that you do not
see today
Do not Do not Do not hurt
you how a Tengteng
did not shoot ah
how do you Tengteng
Stop it Stop it hurt
you because
I told everyone
to camp together
so unhappy ah
I think
we both do not know
what people go the concert
not as together
with you camping and more fun ah
did not feel at ease
because my brother also ah
you see
everyone
I'm not angry with you
I just feel finally
able to get a
chance to date you alone
did not think everyone
of us
this is not really
a separate appointment
that you mean
there next time
how you look so cute ah
you
mess up your hair
you how
angry it
is because you
have not ah
my brother came with Keiji
so angry is not yet
lengthy with Zhao Lei came Why
do you look
glum
menstrual period to the
peace of mind
that you nail the nail into the nail did not
chant
say the lack of a nail
not happen
so I do not believe
the firm
how to you lie
I will give you
a you try to sleep a
little ah will not come out
strong and not
very strong and
it
is very strong hurry hurry hurry
Do you think we try
to play with it
I would not try to tell you
say it
is not strong insecurity
that more than you safe
OMG
brother
are you okay
he's okay
nothing like
a little careful in the future
he is not so big
and tall papier
certainly all right
right I'm fine
Ling Yue is all right for
him to fan
drip down here about
it. This is not
very fragrant
Keiji I took
a small
taste of freshly baked
Sheng
we go for a walk
you want to look for my brother it
so I can refuse to do
the meat is tender
true peace of mind and
Hong Ling always small
Well goes without saying that
it is certainly over
two of the world went to chant
the old lady personally
taste the peace of mind you bake
your brother come looking for you
at home do
not worry about my brother
play with my friends
do not play it too late
to go careful
attention to safety ah
slowly slowly
Why it remains tent ah
you said you wanted to see the stars do not
I'm right here
and then we
pitched a tent
with the stars
that you see
today seems to remember
the good intentions not the stars
but I find this place
for a long time only to find
that we would look good
next time
I'm sorry
did not let you see the stars
this has nothing to
do I'm sorry
fool you like it
so much
Youyou independent radio theater --YoYo Television Series Exclusive